const questions = [
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 27 year old QB for the Kansas City Chiefs passed for 5250 Yards and 41 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Patrick Mahomes"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 26 year old QB for the Buffalo Bills passed for 4283 Yards and 35 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Josh Allen"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 26 year old QB for the CIncInnati Bengals passed for 4475 Yards and 35 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Joe Burrow"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 32 year old QB for the Seattle Seahawks passed for 4282 Yards and 30 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Geno Smith"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 28 year old QB for the Detroit Lions passed for 4438 Yards and 29 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Jared Goff"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 34 year old QB for the MInnesota VikIngs passed for 4547 Yards and 29 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Kirk CousIns"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 39 year old QB for the Green Bay Packers passed for 3695 Yards and 26 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Aaron Rodgers"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 23 year old QB for the Jacksonville Jaguars passed for 4113 Yards and 25 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Trevor Lawrence"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 24 year old QB for the Miami DolphIns passed for 3548 Yards and 25 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Tua Tagovailoa"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 24 year old QB for the Los Angeles Chargers passed for 4739 Yards and 25 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "JustIn Herbert"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 45 year old QB for the Tampa Bay Buccaneers passed for 4694 Yards and 25 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Tom Brady"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 31 year old QB for the Las Vegas Raiders passed for 3522 Yards and 24 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Derek Carr"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 29 year old QB for the Dallas Cowboys passed for 2860 Yards and 23 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Dak Prescott"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 24 year old QB for the Philadelphia Eagles passed for 3701 Yards and 22 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Jalen Hurts"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 35 year old QB for the New Orleans SaInts passed for 2871 Yards and 18 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Andy Dalton"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 23 year old QB for the Chicago Bears passed for 2242 Yards and 17 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "JustIn Fields"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 24 year old QB for the Houston Texans passed for 3118 Yards and 17 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Davis Mills"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 25 year old QB for the Baltimore Ravens passed for 2242 Yards and 17 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Lamar Jackson"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 31 year old QB for the San Francisco 49ers passed for 2437 Yards and 16 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Jimmy Garoppolo"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 34 year old QB for the Denver Broncos passed for 3524 Yards and 16 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Russell Wilson"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 25 year old QB for the New York Giants passed for 3205 Yards and 15 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Daniel Jones"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 29 year old QB for the Atlanta Falcons passed for 2219 Yards and 15 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Marcus Mariota"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 24 year old QB for the New England Patriots passed for 2997 Yards and 14 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Mac Jones"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 25 year old QB for the Arizona CardInals passed for 2368 Yards and 14 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Kyler Murray"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 37 year old QB for the Indianapolis Colts passed for 3057 Yards and 14 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Matt Ryan"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 23 year old QB for the San Francisco 49ers passed for 1374 Yards and 13 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Brock Purdy"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 34 year old QB for the Tennessee Titans passed for 2536 Yards and 13 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Ryan Tannehill"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2022, this 29 year old QB for the WashIngton Football Team passed for 1859 Yards and 12 Touchdowns.",
        answer: "Taylor HeInicke"
    },
]

const NFLPlayerQuestions = questions.sort(() => Math.random() - 0.5)

export default NFLPlayerQuestions;